Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 5. Accessions 2006-207 and 2007-081, 54.75 Linear feet
  - Subseries 2. Photo Shoots
    - Gannett Executives, 1986 April 22 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      35mm color slides (5 sheets), includes images of Douglas McCorkindale, John Quinn, Kathleen Black, John Curley, Thomas Curley
    - Gap, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      35mm color slides (6 sleeves), 2 1/4 in. color transparencies (4 sleeves)
    - Garcia, Julia (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Garden Project - African American Book Project, 1992 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      35mm color slides (7 sheets)
    - Garlic King (Gilroy), 1984 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      35mm color slides (2)
    - Garlic King (Gilroy), 1984 (Flat-box 57, Folder 18)
      Negatives: 5 rolls: 169, 170, 4489, 2 unnumbered
    - Garments for the Homeless, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 11)
      b/w contact sheets (8)
    - Gasse, Jean-Louis, 1986 April 24 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      35mm color slides (3)
    - Gasse, Jean-Louis (Flat-box 54, Folder 1)
      Negatives: rolls: 94026-94029
    - Gauntleh, Suzanne (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Gay Freedom Day Parade, 1989 June 26 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      35mm color slides (3 sheets)
    - General Electric (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - General Mills, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 15)
      2 1/4 in. color transparencies (5 sleeves), 35mm color slides (4 sleeves), World Executive's Digest, July 1994 issue
    - Generic Doctor - Surgeon, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      35mm color slides (5 sheets)
    - Gerlach, Gary, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      35mm color slides (1 sheet)
    - Gerstel, Martin, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      35 mm color slides (3 sheets)
    - Ghiradelli Square, 1983 July (Flat-box 80, Folder 6)
    - Giants fans (Box 83, Folder 10)
      color slide (1)
    - Gilkos Garlic (Flat-box 80, Folder 7)
    - Ginn, Sam (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Golden West Financial, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Gold Rush, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Gold Rush, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Golden Gate Bridge [1 of 4] (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Golden Gate Bridge [1 of 4] (Flat-box 54, Folders 2-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 00462, 00364-00371, 1283-1285, 00348-00351, 03215-03221, 03225, 03327, 03329, 4 unnumbered
    - Golden Gate Bridge [2 of 4] (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Golden Gate Bridge [3 of 4] (Box 77, Folder 14)
      35mm color slides (4 sheets)
    - Golden Gate Bridge [4 of 4] (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Golden Gate Bridge re-decking, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Gorbachev, 1990-1992 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      color contact sheets; color slides
    - Goya, Donna (Levi Strauss), 1991 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Graham, Katherine, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Graham, Odell (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Grants, New Mexico (uranium mine) (Flat-box 80, Folder 8)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 96641-96647
    - Greer, Jon (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Grenada Protest, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Greyhound Strike, 1983 (Flat-box 80, Folder 9)
    - Grigsby, Brandford Powell, Inc. (Box 84, Folder 7)
      color contact sheets
    - Grigsby, Brandford (Powell Inc.) (Flat-box 80, Folder 10)
    - Grimm, Corinne (computer kid) (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Grimm, Corinne (computer kid) (Flat-box 80, Folder 11)
    - Ground Strike, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Guglielemi, Joe (Taligent) (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Guns/Society (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Gyuto Monks, 1991 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Gyuto Monks, 1991 (Flat-box 80, Folder 12)
    - Haas, Robert (CEO, Levi Strauss) (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Hannum, Jill (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Happy Face Collector (Box 85, Folder 2)
      b/w contact sheets
    - Happy Face Collector (Flat-box 80, Folder 13)
    - Harmonic Covergence, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Harris, Jackee (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Harris, Mel (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Hart, Gary, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Harvey, Will, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Hayden, Tom (Flat-box 80, Folder 14)
    - Health Center, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Heart Implant, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Helmond, Katherine (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Hemphill, Susan (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Henderson, Ricky (Flat-box 80, Folder 15)
    - Herion Addict (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Herrera, Oscar, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Highway 1 Mudslide (Box 85, Folders 14-15)
    - Hippies (Box 85, Folder 16)
      b/w print; b/w contact sheets
    - Hippies (Flat-box 80, Folder 16)
    - Hit and Run Driver, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Hoffman-Rubin Debate, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - Holiday Shoppers (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Hollywood - Day in the Life Of (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Homeless (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Homeless (Flat-box 80, Folder 17)
    - Homeless Census (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Homeless Kids School (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Homeopathy (Box 86, Folders 6-8)
    - Homeopathy (Box 87, Folders 1-2)
    - Hong-Kingston, Maxine, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Honolulu, 1991 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Hooks, Jan (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Hopi Relocation (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Horses (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - House at Sunset, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - House Husband, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Howard, Andy, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Hudson, Rock and Doris Day, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 11)
      color slides; color print (1)
    - Hummingbird, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Humphrey the Whale, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Hundred Mile Run (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Indian Activist, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Inner City Schools (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Inuvic/Olympic Torch, 1997 November (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Irvine, Sister Marion (Box 88, Folders 1-2)
    - Islands, 1984 March (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Israel Settlers, 1985 July (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Jackson, Reverend Donald (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Jackson Supporters, 1988 March (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Jacuzzi, Roy, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Jamestown Gold Mine, 1984 January 4 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Japanese Americans, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Japanese Americans, 1986 (Flat-box 80, Folder 18)
    - Jayme, Bill (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Jazzercise (Judy Missett), 1985 December (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Jeanty, Philippe (chef), 1985 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Jesuit Track Stars (Flat-box 80, Folder 19)
    - Jews in America (Box 89, Folders 3-5)
    - Jillian, Ann (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Jill St. John (food) (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Jobs, Steve (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Don, 1985 September (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Jolson, Joseph (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Jones, Stephen, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Jones, Stephen, 1983 (Flat-box 80, Folder 20)
    - Jordan Winery (Flat-box 81, Folder 1)
    - Judge Wapner, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Just Desserts, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Karate Kid, 1985 January (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Keach, Stacey (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Kidoo, Forbes (island houseboat), 1984 April (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Kite Festivals (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Labor Day travel & gas prices, 1986 August (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Ladies Against Women (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - LA Dodgers (Box 90, Folder 7)
      caption sheet only
    - Landscapes (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Larroquette, John (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Larson, Gary (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Las Vegas Wedding (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Leach, Robin (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Leonard, George (akido master) (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Lettuce Growers (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Levee Break, 1983 March (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - LeVey, Anton, 1986 January (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Levi Strauss (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Lewis, Huey, 1985 January (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Lexicus (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Lick Observatory, 1988 May (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Limo Fraud (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Lindow, Dr. Steven (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Little Red Riding Hood (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Loo, Tim and Mary, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Los Angeles Olympics (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Lottery, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Louisiana Pacific, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Louisiana Pacific Strike, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Low Income Family (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Low Income Housing, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Low Income Senior Center, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Low Riders, 1983 March (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Lucas Film Games, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Lucas Film Games, 1988 (Flat-box 81, Folder 2)
    - Maids, Inc., 1990 June (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Maillaird, Charlotte, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Major League Baseball, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Marijuana Eradication (Box 92, Folder 7)
      b/w prints
    - Marijuana Raid, Humboldt, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      color slide; b/w contact sheets
    - Marijuana Raid, Humboldt, 1985 (Flat-box 81, Folder 3)
      b/w negatives (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - Marijuana Raid, Kalifornien (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Marin County (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Martin Luther King Parade, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Mastrov, Mark (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Max, Peter (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Maynard, Robert (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Maytag, Fritz (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Maytag, Fritz (Flat-box 81, Folder 4)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 61751-61752
    - McCloud River/Hearst Estate (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - McCullouch, Frank (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - McDonald, Rebecca (Tenneco) (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - McKesson Corp. (Flat-box 81, Folder 5)
    - McLaclin, Kyle (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Medical (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Meese, Ed (Box 93, Folder 10)
      contact sheets and negatives attached in envelopes
    - Mercenary Soldiers, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Merrill, Richard, 1989 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Mexican Food (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Mills, Donna, 1986 September (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Model Mugging, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Model Mugging, 1988 (Flat-box 81, Folder 6)
    - Mondavi, Robert, 1987 (Flat-box 81, Folder 7)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 02187-02188, 29665-29666
    - Mondale, Eleanor (Flat-box 81, Folder 8)
    - Mondavi, Robert, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Montana Drought (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Montana, Joe (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Montgomery, H. Dubose, 1986 May (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Moore, Gordon (Intel) (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Moore, Mary Tyler (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Morgan, Barbara - KPIX (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Moses, Edwin (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Mother of Mask kid (movie), 1987 July (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Mothers Who Teach their Kids at Home (Flat-box 81, Folder 9)
      color negatives: rolls: 85798-85803
    - Mother Theresa (Box 94, Folder 13)
      b/w prints, negatives
    - Mountain Bikes (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Mount Hood (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Mount St. Helens (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Muller, Mary, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Nachman, Gerald, 1986 May (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Nag, Ronjon (Lexicus) (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Name Project, 1987 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Name Project, 1987 (Flat-box 81, Folder 10)
    - Napa Valley, 1984 June 8 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - Napa Valley, 1984 June 8 (Flat-box 81, Folder 11)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 13381-13384, 13393-13394
    - Navajo Storm Rescue (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Navajo Storm Rescue (Flat-box 81, Folder 12)
    - Navarro, Kim (rollerblader), 1994 May (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - New Car Sales, 1986 August (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Newton, Wayne, 1984 November 19 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - New US Citizens (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Nietschmann, Bernard, 1992 August 17 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Nisshinbo Cotton Processing Plant (Box 95, Folders 7-8)
    - Norman, Donald (Box 95, Folder 9-10)
    - North Face (clothing) (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Nourse, James (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Nuke Dump Town (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Oakland Hills Fire (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Oakland Hills Fire (Box 99, Folders 1-3)
    - O'Conner, Sandra Day, 1986 July 17 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Oldest living heart transplant, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Olson, Jenny and carl Bruce Knapper (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Owades, Ruth, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Owens, Bill (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Pascale, Richard (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Patagonia (clothing) (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Peace Demo (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Pearl Harbor (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Pearl Harbor (Box 97, Folders 1-5)
    - Pearl Harbor (Franklin B. Van Valkenburgh) (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Pearl Harbor (Eugene Leach) (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Penguins, 1990 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Penn and Teller, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Personal Trainers, 1987 September (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Peterson, Donald, 1985 January (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Pierson, Kathy (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Porn District (San Francisco), 1986 June (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Portfolio - Environmental Portrait (no executive) (Box 98, Folder 9)
      color slides; 1 color print
    - Preston Vineyards, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Pred, Elenore (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Prenatal Care (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Prevention (Box 99, Folders 4-5)
    - Prison Labor (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Prison Labor (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Pro-Choice Demo (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Produce Lab, 1987 September (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Quinn, Anthony (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Rainbow Gathering, 1983 (Box 100, Folders 4-5)
    - Rainbow Village, Berkeley, CA, 1986 (Flat-box 81, Folder 13)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 96072, 96075
    - Rajneesh, 1984 (Box 100, Folders 7-8)
    - Rajneesh, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Raymond, Reverend Hope, 1986 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Recycling, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Reed, Ishmael (Box 101, Folders 4-5)
    - Reid, Don (Wells Fargo), 1985 November (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Reinstein, Harry, 1988 March (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Reverse sexist advertisements (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Reynolds, Burt (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Ride and Tie, 1983 June (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Ride and Tie, 1983 June (Flat-box 81, Folder 14)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 2426-2427
    - Riney, Hal (Box 101, Folder 11)
      color slides; color contact sheets; 1 color negative
    - Robards, Jason, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Robards, Jason, 1988 (Flat-box 81, Folder 15)
    - Rockwell International - Satellite (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Rocky Horror Cult (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Rookie Players (Box 101, Folder 14)
      2 1/4 in color transparencies
    - Russell (President of Visa), 1988 November (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Sadler, Elsie (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Saint James, Margo (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Salama, Moktar (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Salem, Oregon (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Salem, Oregon (Flat-box 81, Folder 16)
    - Salvadorian Refugees (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Sanctuary Movement (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Sanctuary Movement (Flat-box 81, Folder 17)
    - San Francisco Ballet (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - San Francisco Cityscapes (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - San Francisco Earthquake, 1989 (Flat-box 81, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco Girl's Chorus (Flat-box 81, Folder 19)
    - San Francisco International Airport (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - San Quentin Prison (Box 102, Folder 12)
      1 b/w print; photocopies; b/w contact with negatives attached
    - San Quentin Prison (Flat-box 82, Folder 1)
    - Santa Clauses (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Santa Cruz (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Santeria (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Schlage Lock Div. (Jerold Tuft), 1987-1988 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - School Children in California (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Schrier, Eric, 1988 December (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Schultz, Charles (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Science Education, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Scottish Rights Day (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Sebastini, Sam and Vicki (Box 103, Folder 9)
      color slides; color internegative (1)
    - Seismograph, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Severance, Joan, 1988 February (Box 103, Folder 11)
      b/w contact sheets; b/w prints
    - Severance, Joan, 1988 February (Flat-box 82, Folder 2)
      b/w negatives: rolls: C1-C7, C9-C14, 061590 #15A
    - Sexologists (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Seymour, Jane (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Shapiro, Francine (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Sheehan, Patty (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Sheep/Lambing/Spring (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Shopping Crowds (after Christmas), 1985 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Shuttle Families (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Single Dad (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Sister Sadie (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Sleep Doctor (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Sleep Doctor (Flat-box 82, Folder 3)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 99854-99855
    - Smith & Hawken - family scenes (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Smith & Hawken - farm life (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Lee (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Martin Cruz (Box 104, Folder 12)
      color slides; b/w contact sheets and corresponding negatives
    - Smith, Scott (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Scott (Flat-box 82, Folder 4)
    - Smolan, Rick (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Soldier of Fortune (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Solectron (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Solomon, Russ (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Sorenson, Keith (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Specialized Bikes (Box 105, Folders 5-6)
    - Spider Webs (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Sports (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Sports (Flat-box 82, Folder 5)
    - Sports - Business Management (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Sports Fans (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Sports - Hammer Throwing (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Stassen, Harold (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Steel (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Stewart, Jimmy (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Stowaway (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Stress Clinic (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Suhre, Jim (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Summer Recreation (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Sunsets (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Sun Valley (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Sun Valley (Flat-box 82, Folder 6)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 91257-91265
    - Super Bowl XIX (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl XIX (Flat-box 82, Folder 7)
      b/w negatives; color negatives
    - Surfers (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Swain, Mike (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Swimming - USA Swim Meet (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Swoboda, Ron (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Syncronized Swimming (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Tandy, Jessica (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Tattoo Man (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Teddy Ruxpin Bear, 1985 December (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, Debi (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Thomas, Debi (Flat-box 82, Folder 8)
      b/w negatives: rolls: C1-C11
    - TKO Farms (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Tompkins, Susie (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Tooby, John and Leda Cosmides (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Tourists in San Francisco (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Track and Field - Bruce Jenner Classic (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Track and Field - Leslie Maxie (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Track and Field - Pepsi (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Track and Field - Sand W Modesto Invitational, 1984 May 12 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Track and Field - S&W Modesto Field (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Tucker, Michael (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Tutu, Desmond (Flat-box 82, Folder 9)
    - Tuolumne River, 1983 July (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Tutu, Desmond (Box 108, Folder 4)
      color prints
    - UC Berkeley Chocolate Professor (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkeley - minority journalism (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Ullman, Tracy (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - US Navy/Russian Spy, 1985 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - USS Missouri, 1986 July (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - USS Missouri, 1986 July (Flat-box 82, Folder 10)
    - Uston, Ken (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Valentine's Day, 1987 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Vander Kamp, John, 1989 January (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Van Dyke, Dick (Box 108, Folder 13)
      color slides (2)
    - VF Corp (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Voter Registration, 1984 September (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - Waiters on Wheels (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Wald, Johanna H., 1988 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Waken, Christopher, 1986 October (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Walker, Alice, 1984 November (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Watches (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - Water Balloons (Sun Microsystems) (Box 108, Folder 21)
      color slides; b/w prints
    - Water Polo (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Weather Art (Box 108, Folder 23)
    - Wedding Prep (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - White Water Rafting - American River (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Wind Surfing, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Wine Auction, 1983 June (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Wine Auction, 1983 June (Flat-box 82, Folder 11)
    - Wine Country Balloon Tours, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Wine Country Inn (Flat-box 82, Folder 12)
    - Wine Growers, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Wine/Travel (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Woman Doctor, 1988 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Women Winemakers, 1985 (Flat-box 82, Folder 13)
    - Women & Guns, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Women's Marathon (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Women in Business (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Women's Volleyball (NCAA Championships), 1983 November 12 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Women Who Drink (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Women Winemakers, 1985 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Working Moms, 1986 November (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Working Mothers, 1986 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Working Mothers, 1986 (Flat-box 82, Folder 14)
    - Working Poor, 1987 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - World War II Veteran (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Yosemite, 1986 (Half-box 110, Folder 1)
    - Yosemite Flooding, 1983 (Half-box 110, Folder 2)
    - Young, Father Ernle (Half-box 110, Folder 3)
    - Young, Steve (Half-box 110, Folder 4)
    - Zappa, Frank, 1984 (Half-box 110, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3. Negatives
    This subsubseries contains negatives relating to Menuez's photography jobs. Not all rolls of negatives are complete, and not all negative rolls have corresponding contact sheets. Corresponding contact sheets may be found in Series 5, Subseries 1. Jobs and Series 1, Subseries 1. Jobs, Subsubseries 9. Farallon Computing.
    Subseries 3, Negatives, is CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes. Researchers should refer to the corresponding contact sheets in Series 5, Subseries 1. Jobs or Series 1, Subseries 1. Jobs (for Farallon). To request copies of images, please refer to job and roll number.
    - Accel, 1995 (Flat-box 28, Folders 1-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 08040-08065.
    - Accel, 1995 December - 1997 August (Flat-box 49, Folders 11-16)
      Negatives: rolls: 09924-09945, 1-27.
    - Agenda, 1992 (Flat-box 28, Folders 4-8)
      Contains 569 color negatives; Rolls: 51569, 51570, 51572, 51574-51576, 51597, 53062-53067, 53069-53070, 53072, 53073, 53076, 53080, 53084, 53011, 53114, 53115, 53119, 53127, 53128, 53131, 53135, 53137-53139, 53154-53157, 53159, 53161-53165, 53168.
      Note: there are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 52163, 53071, 53117, 53117, 53129, 53130, 53160. There no negatives for rolls 53115 and 53160.
    - Autodesk Annual Report (4 folders), 1996 (Box-folder 28-9, Box-folder 29-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 12633-12653, 12665-12672, 12674-12680, 12717-12734, 12736-12750, 01482-01486, 85514-85540, 11922-11928.
      Roll 12725 is incomplete, negatives 1-18 are missing; roll 12739 is incomplete, negatives 2-6 are missing.
    - Beckman, 1992 (Flat-box 29, Folders 4-8)
      Negatives: rolls: 80374-80400, 80696-80698, JS1-10, "Beckman Office in Mexico: 1-2”, 0007-0013.
      Notes: re: roll 0008: business card attached: Werner Kirchoff, notes made on plastic: Kirch, Turner, Krohne; John Turner; Krohne and Kirchoff; roll 0009: business cards attached: John Tuner, Hartmut Wetzel, notes made on plastic: employee manning Beckman "hottie"; roll 0010: Business card attached: Karel Krohne, notes made on plastic: Kirch, Turner, Krohne; John Turner; Krohne and Kirchoff; roll 0012: notes made on plastic: Jeanne Jacquot; roll 0013: Business cards attached: Dr. Hans-Jurgen Schneider, Bernd Böcke.
    - Beckman (8 folders), 1989-1993 (Box-folder 29-9, Box-folder 30-7)